Guide to the Records of Athletics Programs at New York University RG.41
New York University Archives
- RG 41.3: Fencing, 1925-1995
  - Fencing Team Clippings, Rosters, & Press Releases, 1963-1964; cuid15287 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Fencing Team Rosters, Schedules, Clippings, & Press Releases, 1964-1965; cuid15288 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Fencing Team Rosters, Clippings, & Press Releases, 1965-1966; cuid15289 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Intercollegiate Fencing Association Championships, 1969-1973; cuid15290 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Intercollegiate Fencing Association Championships, 1956, 1959-1967; cuid15291 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Fencing Team Rosters, Clippings, Press Releases, 1966-1967; cuid15292 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Fencing Team Schedules, Clippings, Rosters, & Press Releases, 1967-1968; cuid15293 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Women's Fencing Season, 1967-1968; cuid15294 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Fencing Team Rosters, Schedules, Clippings, & Press Releases, 1968-1969; cuid15295 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - 72nd Intercollegiate Fencing Association Championships at NYU, 1969; cuid15296 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Intercollegiate Fencing Association Championships, 1952, 1967, 1969, 1970, 1971, 1972, 1978, 1980; cuid15297 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Interscholastic (Schoolboy) Fencing Tournament, 1963-1968; cuid15298 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Women's Season Papers, 1963-1964; cuid15299 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Intercollegiate Women's Fencing Association Championship Material, 1964-1968; cuid15300 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Women's Fencing Records, Rosters, and Materials, 1964-1966; cuid15301 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Women's Fencing Materials, 1966-1968; cuid15302 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Women's Fencing Rosters, Schedules, and Correspondence, 1968-1969; cuid15303 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Fencing Team Rosters, Press Releases, and Schedules, 1969-1970; cuid15304 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Fencing Team Rosters, Schedules, Clippings, and Press Releases, 1970-1971; cuid15305 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Interscholastic (Schoolboy) Fencing Tournament, 1964-1970; cuid15306 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Sally Pechinsky Interview, 1970; cuid15307 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Women's Fencing Team Rosters, Schedules, Clippings, and Press Releases, 1969-1970; cuid15308 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Walter Krause - Outstanding Athlete Press Release, 1970; cuid15309 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Fencing Captain Wayne Krause Press Release, 1970; cuid15310 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Amateur Fencers League of America - Fencing Rules and Manual, 1970; cuid15311 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Fencing Coach Csajaghy Retires, 1970 15 July; cuid15312 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Fencing Prospects, 1970; cuid15313 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Sebastiani to Coach, 1970; cuid15314 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Intercollegiate Fencing Association Championship, 1970 5 March; cuid15315 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Women's Fencing Team Clippings, Rosters, Schedules, and Press Releases, 1970-1973; cuid15316 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Fencing Team Schedules, Press Releases, Clippings, and Rosters, 1971-1972; cuid15317 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Fencing Team Schedules, Pamphlets, Clippings, and Press Releases, 1971-1972; cuid15318 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Intercollegiate Women's Fencing Association Material, 1952-1978; cuid15319 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - IWFA Championship at NYU, 1970; cuid15320 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Women's and Men's Fencing Season Materials, 1972-1973; cuid15321 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Women's Fencing Team Schedules, Rosters, Score Cards, and Rankings, 1973-1974; cuid15322 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Intercollegiate Fencing Association Championship, 1973; cuid15323 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Women's Fencing Team Materials, 1974-1976; cuid15324 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Women's Fencing Press Release, 1970; cuid15325 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Fencing Team Programs, 1985-1986; cuid15326 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Fencing Programs and a Championship Ribbon, 1994-1995; cuid15327 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Abby, Carol, 1965-1966; cuid15328 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Apostol, Paul, 1966-1972; cuid15329 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Castello, James M., 1946-1966; cuid15330 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Castello, Julio M., 1935-1969; cuid15331 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Csajaghy, Bela, 1968; cuid15332 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Dasaro, Mike, 1958-1964; cuid15333 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Davis, Albert E., 1965-1966; cuid15334 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - DeCapriles, Jose R., 1969; cuid15335 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - DeCapriles, Miguel, 1952-1967; cuid15336 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Gaylor, Michael, 1967-1968; cuid15337 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Jones, Julia, Undated; cuid15338 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Masin, George, 1966-1968; cuid15339 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - McGlennon, Harriet, 1941; cuid15340 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Menendez, Ableardo, Undated; cuid15341 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Peredo, Al, 1961-1964; cuid15342 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Sebastiani, Michel, Undated; cuid15343 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - William, Thomas, 1952; cuid15344 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Wallner, Herman, 1952; cuid15345 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Saber, foil, and épée, undated (Box 279)
- RG 41.4: Football, 1889-1967
  History of Football at NYU
  The NYU football team was founded in 1873. It was one of the first university-sponsored teams in the U.S., preceded only by Princeton, Rutgers, and Yale. During its inaugural season, NYU lost its only game, to the Stevens Institute of Technology, which was also a brand new team.
  Few documents from NYU football's early years have survived, but existing records indicate few wins early on. Following the acquisition of the University Heights campus in 1894, the team began playing and practicing on Ohio Field.
  NYU was integral to the regulation of college athletics in the early 20th century, helping to found the Intercollegiate Athletic Association of the United States, precursor to the National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA).
  The late 1920s became known as the "Golden Era" of NYU football. The school played a number of games at the new Yankee Stadium, and coach John Meehan led the team to 49 wins and only 15 losses. When Meehan left in 1931, the team was unable to continue its earlier successes, in part because World War II drained the player pool and financial resources.
  After the war, the team tried to recapture its previous popularity and success, but increased funds did not lead to increasing interest or ticket sales. In 1953 the team was disbanded. Football made a short return in 1964 as a club sport but never caught on and was officially discontinued in 1967 because of lack of interest.
  This series contains a number of player biographies, including newspaper clippings and NYU press information on specific players, team rosters and schedules, statistics, game programs, and NYU press releases concerning the team. These materials range in date from 1889 until 1967.
  - Football Hall of Fame Papers, 1947-1955; cuid15346 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - College Stadium Statistics, Undated; cuid15347 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - History of the NYU Football Team, 1967; cuid15348 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Football Team Notes and Roster, 1889; cuid15349 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Football Clipping, 1921 4 June; cuid15350 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - NYU Football Squads Personnel, 1928-1945; cuid15351 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Football Team Programs, Pamphlets, and Roster, 1928; cuid15352 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - "Football Facts" and Team Roster, 1929; cuid15353 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - NYU vs. Columbia, Fordham, Rutgers, 1922-1964; cuid15354 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Football Team Rosters and Press Releases, 1933-1939; cuid15355 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Football Team Narratives, Rosters, and "Football Facts", 1930-1939; cuid15356 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Football Team Clippings, 1930; cuid15357 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Football Team Clippings, 1931; cuid15358 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Football Team Statistics, 1932; cuid15359 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Football Team Clippings, 1932; cuid15360 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Football Team Roster and Press Release and "Football Facts", 1933; cuid15361 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Football Team Clippings, 1933; cuid15362 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Football Team Statistics, Rosters, and "Football Facts", 1934; cuid15363 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Football Clippings, 1934; cuid15364 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Football Team Rosters and Statistics, 1935; cuid15365 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Football Team Information and Rosters, 1935; cuid15366 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Football Team Clippings, 1935; cuid15367 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - "Football Facts", 1937; cuid15368 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Football Team Statistics, 1937; cuid15369 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Football Team Clippings, 1937; cuid15370 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Football Team Statistics, Rosters, Press Releases, and "Football Facts", 1938; cuid15371 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Football Team Clippings, 1938; cuid15372 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Football Team Statistics and "Football Facts", 1939; cuid15373 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Football Team Clippings, 1939; cuid15374 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Football Team Rosters, Statistics, Press Releases, and "Football Facts", 1940; cuid15375 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Football Team Clippings, 1940; cuid15376 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Freshmen Football Statistics and Roster, 1940; cuid15377 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - 1911 Football Schedule, cuid15378 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Football Schedule and Trinity vs. NYU Game Program, 1912; cuid15379 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Trinity College vs. NYU Game Program, 1913; cuid15380 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Rensselaer Pol. Institute vs. NYU Program, 1914 24 Oct; cuid15381 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Football Game Programs, 1915; cuid15382 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Football Game Programs, 1916; cuid15383 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Football Game Programs, 1917; cuid15384 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Trinity vs. NYU Program, 1919; cuid15385 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Football Schedule, 1920; cuid15386 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Football Schedule and Programs, 1922; cuid15387 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Football Game Programs, 1924; cuid15388 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - NYU vs. Niagra, 1925; cuid15389 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Football Game Programs, 1926; cuid15390 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Football Game Programs, 1927; cuid15391 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Football Programs, 1928; cuid15392 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Football Programs, 1929; cuid15393 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Football Game Programs, 1931; cuid15394 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Football Game Programs, 1932; cuid15395 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Football Game Programs, 1933; cuid15396 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Football Game Programs, 1934; cuid15397 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Football Game Programs, 1935; cuid15398 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Football Schedule, 1938; cuid15399 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Football Game Programs, 1939; cuid15400 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Football Game Programs, 1940; cuid15401 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Varsity Football Statistics, 1945-1946; cuid15402 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Football Game Programs, 1941; cuid15403 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Football Statistics and Game Programs, 1946; cuid15404 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Football Game Programs, 1947-1948; cuid15405 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Football Game Programs, 1949; cuid15406 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Football Game Programs, 1950; cuid15407 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Football Game Programs, 1951; cuid15408 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Football Game Programs, 1952; cuid15409 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Agnone, John J. Player Biography, 1950; cuid15410 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Barnes, Hester Player Biography, 1938; cuid15411 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Bernstein, Charles Player Biography, 1947; cuid15412 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Bonacorsa, Joe Player Biography, 1958-1964; cuid15413 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Boroff, Paul E. Player Biography, 1942; cuid15414 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Bunyan, John T. Player Biography, 1949; cuid15415 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Burney, Bill Player Biography, 1952; cuid15416 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Campanis, Alexander Player Biography, 1940; cuid15417 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Carapella, Al Player Biography, 1966; cuid15418 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Cestary, Roy Player Biography, 1949; cuid15419 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Cherico, Ross Player Biography, 1944-1945; cuid15420 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Collins, Leo V. Player Biography, 1927-1930; cuid15421 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Comerford, Charles A. Player Biography, 1934; cuid15422 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Concannon, Ernie Player Biography, 1962; cuid15423 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Connolly, Robert V. Player Biography, 1936-1945; cuid15424 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Connor, John J. (Dutch) Player Biography, 1952; cuid15425 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Consagra, Joseph Player Biography, 1939-1968; cuid15426 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Devore, Hugh Player Biography, 1950-1953; cuid15427 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Dickson, George Player Biography, 1952; cuid15428 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - DiGaspari, Vince Player Biography, 1951; cuid15429 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Dintman, Herbert Player Biography, 1950; cuid15430 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Dowd, Dan Player Biography, 1962; cuid15431 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Dunney, Howard E. Player Biography, 1939; cuid15432 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Feibish, Bernard Player Biography, 1946-1947; cuid15433 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Furiel, Ralph Player Biography, 1947; cuid15434 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Gersh, Edward Player Biography, 1943-1945; cuid15435 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Gladchuck, Chet Player Biography, 1946; cuid15436 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Jackson, John Player Biography, 1968; cuid15437 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Healey, Joseph Player Biography, 1956-1978; cuid15438 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Lassman, Alfred Player Biography, 1930-1933; cuid15439 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Lassman, Alfred Clippings, 1928-1930; cuid15440 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Intercollegiate Football 1869-1934, cuid15441 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Football Policy Discontinuation, 1941-1942; cuid15442 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Football Policy Discontinuation, 1941-1942; cuid15443 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Student Petition on Discontinuation of Football Program, 1941; cuid15444 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Football Clippings, 1941; cuid15445 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Varsity Football Statistics and Clippings, 1941; cuid15446 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Football Resinstated Clippings, 1944; cuid15447 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Varsity Football Statistics and Press Release, 1945; cuid15448 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Football Clippings, 1944; cuid15449 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Football Clippings and Press Information, 1945; cuid15450 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Football Clippings, 1945; cuid15451 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Football Statistics and Press Information, 1946; cuid15452 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Football Clippings, 1946; cuid15453 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Football Statistics and Press Information, 1947; cuid15454 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Football Clippings, 1947; cuid15455 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Football Statistics and Press Information, 1948; cuid15456 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Football Clippings, 1948; cuid15457 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Football Statistics and Press Information, 1949; cuid15458 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Football Clippings, 1949; cuid15459 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Football Statistics and Press Information, 1950; cuid15460 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Football Clippings, 1950; cuid15461 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Football Statistics and Press Information, 1951; cuid15462 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Football Clippings, 1951; cuid15463 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Football Statistics and Press Information, 1952; cuid15464 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Football Clippings, 1952; cuid15465 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Club Football Press Information, 1964; cuid15466 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Club Football Statistics and Press Information, 1964; cuid15467 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Football Policy/Discontinuation, 1953; cuid15468 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Football Clippings, 1964; cuid15469 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Club Football Statistics and Press Information, 1965; cuid15470 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Club Football Clippings, 1965; cuid15471 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Club Football Clippings, 1965; cuid15472 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Club Football Statistics and Press Information, 1966; cuid15473 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Club Football Statistics and Press Information, 1966; cuid15474 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Club Football Clippings, 1966; cuid15475 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Football Discontinuation, 1967; cuid15476 (Box 37, Folder 16)
- RG 41.5: Gymnastics, 1898-1906
  History of Gymnastics at NYU
  Gymnastics makes a brief appearance in the history of athletics at NYU. It was first practiced in 1894 after the addition of the University Heights campus in the Bronx. In March of 1897 the Athletic Association held the first dual gymnastic meet for prizes. There, NYU defeated Lehigh University. Two years later NYU hosted its first intercollegiate gymnastics event with 19 other colleges. Events included the horizontal bar, tumbling, club swinging, fence vaulting, rings, parallel bars, high jump, and the side horse. World War I interfered with the burgeoning team's growth, and the team was disbanded in 1919.
  This series is comprised of New York University gymnastics meet programs and tickets ranging from 1898 to 1906.
  - Gymnastics Programs & Tickets, 1898; cuid15477 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Gymnastics Programs, 1899; cuid15478 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Gymnastics Meet Flyer, Undated; cuid15479 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Gymnastics Programs, 1900; cuid15480 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Gymnastics Program, 1902; cuid15481 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Gymnastics Programs, 1903; cuid15482 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Gymnastics Programs, 1904; cuid15483 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Gymnastics Program, 1905; cuid15484 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- RG 41.6: Track and Field, 1899-2007
  History of Track and Field at NYU
  The earliest mention of New York University's track and field team is in the University Heights 1896 Violet yearbook. Since then, NYU has aided in the training of many track and field Olympians. The earliest track meets were held outside at Ohio Field on the University Heights campus, which was constructed in 1900. In 1912, the New York University Track Association held its first annual indoor meet at the 22nd Regiment Armory. In 1971 coach Joe Healey was named the United States Track Coaches Association Coach of the Year.
  Today men's and women's track and field teams continue to compete at the varsity level in the University Athletic Association Conference.
  The Track and Field Series contains track event programs, statistics, and newspaper clippings as well as player biographies. Track sports began at NYU in 1895, and this series has records dating back to 1899 and continuing somewhat sporadically through 2007.
  Men's and women's track and field results for 2003-2014 are located in Archives H. Men's and women's cross country results for 2000-2014 are located in Archives H.
  - Track and Field Program, 1899; cuid15485 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Track and Field Program, 1901; cuid15486 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Track and Field Program, 1903; cuid15487 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Track and Field Program, 1909; cuid15488 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Track and Field Programs, 1912; cuid15489 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Track and Field Program, 1923; cuid15490 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Track and Field Program, 1933; cuid15491 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Track and Field Schedule, 1944; cuid15492 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Track and Field Programs, 1971; cuid15493 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Track and Field Statistics and Clippings, 1963-1964; cuid15494 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Cross Country, Indoor, & Outdoor Track, 1945-1946; cuid15495 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Cross Country, Indoor, & Outdoor Track and Field, 1946-1947; cuid15496 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Track and Field Schedule, 1994-1995; cuid15497 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Cross Country, 2007; cuid15498 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Castro, Frank Biography, 1923-July-12; cuid15499 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Dyce, Byron Biography, 1966-1969; cuid15500 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Edwards, Phil Biography, 1970-1971; cuid15501 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Ellis, Larry Biography, 1951-1952; cuid15502 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Engel, Martin Biography, 1952; cuid15503 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Healey, Joseph F. Biography, 1957-1969; cuid15504 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Hooten, Denise Biography, 1972; cuid15505 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Marshall, Shelly Biography, 1971-December-2; cuid15506 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Mondschein, Irving Biography, 1948-1949; cuid15507 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Pearman, Reginald Biography, 1947-1948; cuid15508 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Sieja, Stanley Biography, 1949; cuid15509 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Schoolman, Irving Biography, 1956-1961; cuid15510 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Toussaint, Cheryl Biography, 1971-1972; cuid15511 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Weber, Jake Biography, 1946-1948; cuid15512 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Wedderburn, Jim Biography, 1961; cuid15513 (Box 39, Folder 30)
- RG 41.7: Athletics Department administrative files, 1945-1980
  This series contains a correspondence file of Director of Athletics Dan Quilty. Quilty served in this position from 1972-1996. The file represents several years of communication with Vice President for Student Affairs Jane Maggin.
  - Athletic Department Administrative Files, 1976-1980; cuid15514 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- RG 41.8: Coles Sports Center, 1981-2010
  History of Coles Sports Center
  The Coles Sports Center, located at 181 Mercer Street, was opened in 1981 and named after NYU alumnus and benefactor Jerome S. Coles. The new facilities provided the University, which had recently returned entirely to its downtown campus, with a location for sporting events, team practices, health and wellness activities, and community recreation. The Coles Sports Center served as the home for NYU's NCAA Division III teams and also hosted a number of events including NCAA Men's and Women's National and Regional Championships in basketball and fencing as well as international wrestling and fencing competitions.
  In 2014, NYU announced plans to demolish Coles and build a new facility in its place.
  This series is comprised of Coles Sports & Recreation Center Information Booklets and Program Guides ranging from 1981 to 2010 and arranged chronologically.
  - Coles Sports & Recreation Center Information/Procedures Booklet, 1981-1982; cuid15515 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Coles Sports & Recreation Center Information/Procedures Booklet, 1983-1984; cuid15516 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Coles Sports & Recreation Center Information/Procedures Booklet, 1987-1988; cuid15517 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Coles Sports & Recreation Center Information/Procedures Booklet, 1990-1991; cuid15518 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Coles Sports & Recreation Center Information/Procedures Booklet, 1991-1992; cuid15519 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Coles Sports & Recreation Center Information/Procedures Booklet, 1992-1994; cuid15520 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Coles Sports & Recreation Center Information/Procedures Booklet, 1995-2010; cuid15521 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Coles Program Guide, 1982-1983; cuid15522 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Coles Program Guide, 1983-1984; cuid15523 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Coles Program Guide, 1988-1989; cuid15524 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Coles Program Guide, 1988-1989; cuid15525 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Coles Program Guide, 1990-1991; cuid15526 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Coles Program Guide, 1991-1992; cuid15527 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Coles Program Guide, 1992-1994; cuid15528 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Coles Program Guide, 1996-1997; cuid15529 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Coles Program Guide, 1998-1999; cuid15530 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Coles Program Guide, 1999-2003; cuid15531 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Coles Program Guide, 2004-2005; cuid15532 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Coles Program Guide, 2005-2006; cuid15533 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Coles Program Guide, 2006-2007; cuid15534 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Coles Program Guide, 2007-2008; cuid15535 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Coles Program Guide, 2008-2009; cuid15536 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- RG 41.10: NYU Olympic Athletes
  History of Olympic Athletes at NYU